# Minahil Akhtar

minahilakhtar2235@gmail.com

(815) 513-2697

linkedin.com/in/minahil-akhtar

https://minahilakhtar.com/

### **Summary**

I am a MERN Stack and WordPress Developer with experience in modern technologies such as React.JS, Redux, Node.JS, Express.js, REST APIs, MongoDB, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, and Bootstrap. I am passionate about what I'm doing and see every task as a challenge and an opportunity to get better.

My Personal Website https://minahilakhtar.com

My Portfolio Website https://minahilakhtar.github.io/cv/

#### **Experience**



Chingu

Apr 2023 - Nov 2023 (8 months)

I have worked on chingu as a Front-end Developer at Chingu, collaborating closely with a dynamic team of developers on a wide range of projects.

## **up** Mern Stack Developer

Upwork

Jan 2021 - Present (2 years 11 months)

# Frontend Developer

**Bulls Orbit** 

Mar 2022 - Apr 2023 (1 year 2 months)

I have worked at Bulls Orbit as a Front end developer There I Completed a lot of tasks related to web development.

#### Frontend Web Developer

Frontend Mentor

Mar 2021 - Jan 2022 (11 months)

https://www.frontendmentor.io/profile/minahilakhtar

#### **Education**

#### **⊗**<sup>ℤ™</sup> Zero To Mastery Academy

Full Stack Web Development

Feb 2020 - Mar 2021

The Complete Web Developer in 2023: Zero to Mastery

Skills: API Testing · Databases · JSON · HTTP · CSS3 · Node.js · Express.js · React.js · JavaScript · HTML5

# (A) freeCodeCamp

Front-End Web Development

Jan 2017 - Mar 2018

Created responsive web pages using JS, HTML, CSS, Flexbox/Grid, Bootstrap, visual design and accessibility to build projects: Tribute Page, Survey Form, Product Landing Page, Technical Doc.

# M Army Public School - (APSACS)

Intermediate

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

Digital Marketing - DigiSkills.pk 6727RGTPQ

# Facebook Ads - Asean Online Education AOE 192816199672

CSS & JavaScript - Certification Course - Udemy UC-724f3a84-6e24-4713-9e0f-14228640c28e

## **Google Ads Search Certification**

49530046

- Digital Marketing Master Class FEMPROW
- **The Fundamental Of Digital Maketing** Google Digital Garage WTP FPL EEV
- in JavaScript Essential Training LinkedIn AVsUkDaaMFz2jlx0L\_tjEQ2ayl7l
- in HTML Essential Training LinkedIn Addl3VLWTGsp1hdEL6R35\_6m2Avr
- CSS Essential Training LinkedIn AY26hCblGorlqYc30aeNwOaiuwLE
- Front-End Development Chingu Issued Aug 2023 - Expires Sep 2023

## **Skills**

Responsive Web Design • Team Leadership • Front-end Coding • git github • REST APIs • Express.js • Node.js • Front-End Development • React.js • WordPress